{
    "subject": "resource/1953_Dutch_Grand_Prix",
    "predicate": "ontology/firstDriverTeam",
    "object": "resource/Scuderia_Ferrari",
    "human_readable": "The first driver team for the 1953 Dutch Grand Prix is Scuderia Ferrari.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9866023063659668,
            "question": "For which race was Scuderia Ferrari the first driver team in 1953?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9843815565109253,
            "question": "Who was the first driver team for the 1953 Dutch Grand Prix?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9841899275779724,
            "question": "What was the first driver team for the Dutch Grand Prix of 1953?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9776493906974792,
            "question": "Did Scuderia Ferrari compete in the Dutch Grand Prix in 1953?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9304082989692688,
            "question": "In what year did Scuderia Ferrari win their first Dutch Grand Prix?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9205914735794067,
            "question": "Was Scuderia Ferrari a competing team in the Dutch Grand Prix?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8761345148086548,
            "question": "What year did Scuderia Ferrari compete in the Dutch Grand Prix?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8439461588859558,
            "question": "Which race is Scuderia Ferrari associated with from 1953?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8342808485031128,
            "question": "In what event did Scuderia Ferrari take part in 1953?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7330755591392517,
            "question": "What was the name of the grand prix Scuderia Ferrari participated in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The first driver team for the 1953 Dutch Grand Prix is Scuderia Ferrari.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6352_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what event did Scuderia Ferrari take part in 1953?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6352_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which race is Scuderia Ferrari associated with from 1953?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6352_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year did Scuderia Ferrari compete in the Dutch Grand Prix?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6352_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6352_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6352_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6352_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6352_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6352_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6352_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6352_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6352_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6352_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6352_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have other triples you'd like me to evaluate!  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\n### Explanation:\nThe documents provide information about the 1953 Dutch Grand Prix and mention that Alberto Ascari, who was a Ferrari driver, won the race. Additionally, the document \"117.txt\" specifically mentions Alberto Ascari driving for Ferrari in the 1953 Dutch Grand Prix. Therefore, it supports the statement that Scuderia Ferrari was the first driver team for the 1953 Dutch Grand Prix."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}